Inventory of the Psi Upsilon Records, 1840 - 1972
Psi Upsilon Records1840 - 1972
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Xi Chapter of Psi Upsilon
1000-216
15
16
The Psi Upsilon records consist of materials related to Xi Chapter at Wesleyan University and include constitions, by-laws, minutes, programs, correspondence, invitations, clippings, publications, annals and chronicles, photographs, architectural drawings, and scrapbooks.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Collection Overview
The Psi Upsilon records consist of materials related to Xi Chapter at Wesleyan University and include constitions, by-laws, minutes, programs, correspondence, invitations, clippings, publications, annals and chronicles, photographs, architectural drawings, and scrapbooks.
Collection Arrangement
The records are arranged in the 13 series: Series I. Administrative Records, 1841-1972; Series II. Minutes, 1856-1959; Series III. Correspondence, 1881-1971; Series IV. Scrapbooks, 1863-1901; Series V. Members; Series VI. Initiations, 1884-1971; Series VII. Programs and Events, 1873-1988; Series VIII. Music and Poetry, 1874-1945; Series IX. Clippings, 1891-1957; Series X. Publications, 1855-1953; Series XI. Photographs, 1870-1885; Series XII. Other Records, 1840-1933; and Series XIII. Architectural Drawings, May 1891.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Isaac, Allan Punzalan.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Greek letter societies.; Psi Upsilon Fraternity.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series I. Administrative Records, 1841-1972
  - Consitution of Psi Upsilon Fraternity, Xi Chapter, 1881 (Box shelf)
  - Chronicles of Xi of Psi Upsilon, 1841-1870 (Box shelf)
  - Roll of Honor, June 28, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    List of those who contributed toward the building of the Chapter house
  - Warranty Deed, April 1888 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Note from the Law Office of M. Eugene Culver concerning funds borrowed for purchasing lot, 188(?) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified notes from a meeting of the trustees, December 12, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified notes concerning administrative proceedings, May 14, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - List of names and notes from a meeting of the trustees, June 28, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notes for a resolution concerning the borrowing of funds, February 10, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notes for a resolution passed by the trustees, March 31, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notes for a resolution passed by the trustees, July 13, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report on visit to the Xi Chapter by Stephen G. Kent, April 12, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and expenditures reported by the assistant treasurer, June 1936 - June 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report of visit to Xi Chapter with editing marks, February 27, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - List of unofficial functions of various positions in fraternity compiled by 1942 Committee on Fraternity and Chapter Workings, May 8, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Outline of meeting ritual and accompanying envelope addressed to Mr. Joseph Rigali, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notes concerning transfer of funds and purchase of property from Silliman to Colegrove families, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten by-laws beginning with Article III, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Typewritten by-laws beginning with Article I, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten by-laws of the trustees of Psi Upsilon, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten amendment to the fraternity constitution, June 29, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fragments of typewritten by-laws, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Typewritten by-laws, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Typewritten by-laws, labeled "Constitution of the Psi Upsilon Fraternity," undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Typewritten Constitution of Psi Upsilon, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Typewritten Constitution of the Psi Upsilon Fraternity, including blank outline of traditional constitution, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Various fragments of fraternity by-laws, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Records of all the Conventions of the Psi Upsilon Fraternity, 1841-1872 (Box 9)
  - Guest book of Xi of Psi Upsilon, May 3, 1921-February 20, 1928 (Box 9)
  - By-Laws of the Xi Chapter of the Psi Upsilon Fraternity, undated (Box 9)
    Inside cover marked "Xi Chapter of" and "G.S. Harrison"
  - Appointments, 1901-1920 (Box 9)
    List of initiated members
  - Constitution By-Laws and Minutes of the Chique Chaque Eating Club, undated (Box 9)
  - Xi Chapter of Psi Upsilon Treasurer's Account Book, October 29, 1890-1906 (Box 9)
  - Culturation Committee Xi of Psi Upsilon Memoranda and Suggestions, May 1887 (Box 9)
  - Psi Upsilon By-Laws, undated (Box 9)
  - Chroniclers Records, undated (Box 10)
  - Building fund pledges scrapbook, 1892 (Box 10)
  - The Xi Budget and minutes, 1844-1856 (Box 10)
  - Records of the Trustees of the Xi Chapter of Psi Upsilon Fraternity, February 1, 1919 (Box 10)
    Records from 1867-1919
  - Defunct individual accounts, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
  - Records of receipts and expenses, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Records of accounts, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
  - Record book of the House Committee, about 1910 (Box 10)
  - Constitution with annotated revisions, about 1930s (Box 10)
  - Chronicles of the Xi of Psi U, 1874-1929 (Box 10)
  - Constitution of Psi Upsilon, June 1, 1939 (Box shelf)
    Book printed, signed by the Psi U. Executive Council
- Series II. Minutes, 1856-1959
  - Minute book, Nov. 20, 1843-Nov. 15, 1856 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Feb. 7, 1857-Oct. 25, 1860 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Nov. 2, 1860-Nov. 18, 1864 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Dec. 16, 1864-June 27, 1868 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, July 3, 1868-Sept. 14, 1871 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Sept. 15, 1871-Jun. 22, 1875 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Sept. 10, 1875-Dec. 6, 1878 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Apr. 18, 1879-June 30, 1881 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Sept. 13, 1881-Mar. 28, 1884 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Apr. 18, 1884-Sept. 13, 1887 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Sept. 16, 1887-Oct. 4, 1889 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Oct. 4, 1889-Oct. 29, 1892 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Oct. 29, 1892-June 15, 1894 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, June 23, 1894-Apr. 1898 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Apr. 1, 1898-Dec. 14, 1900 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Dec. 14, 1900-June 20, 1907 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, June 23, 1907-Nov. 2, 1914 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Nov. 2, 1914-Mar. 9, 1923 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Oct. 31, 1928-June 14, 1935 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Sept. 25, 1935-Sept. 30, 1936 (Box shelf)
  - Minute book, Feb. 22, 1955-Feb. 24, 1959 (Box shelf)
  - Meeting minutes, June 24, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 28, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 27, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 26, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 25, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 24, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, October 17, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, October 27, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 29, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 28, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 27, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 27, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 25, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 1902 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 30, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 28, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 27, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 26, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, November 22, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 25, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 18, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes, June 25, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of the Xi Chapter of the Psi Upsilon Fraternity, June 23, 1908-June 15, 1918 (Box 11)
  - Minutes of the Trustee and Association Meetings of the Xi of Psi Upsilon, December 16, 1867-June 28, 1887 (Box 11)
  - Hall of Xi Minutes, January 6, 1926-October 31, 1928 (Box 11)
- Series III. Correspondence, 1881-1971
  - Fundraising letter from D. Ward Northrop, May 1881 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception to "Prof. and Mrs. Harrington," June 28, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception to "Prof. and Mrs. Harrington," June 27, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to Ninth Quadrennial to "Dr. D. Copeland," June 27, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to Ninth Quadrennial, June 27, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception, June 26, 1883 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to parlor concert, May 2, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception, June 24, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to parlor concert, May 1, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - In Memoriam announcement of the death of Prof. Calvin Sears Harrington, addressed to "Prof. Karl P. Harrington," February 16, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to parlor concert, May 14, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception, June 28, 1887 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to Annual Musicale, March 23, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to Ninth Quinquennial Exercises, June 27, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to Annual Musicale, May 31, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitation to annual reception, June 25, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letter from Arthur Sherburne Hardig, April 9, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Charles Flerry(?), including In Memoriam tribute to George W. Pratt and Samuel Wesley Wood, April 13, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Charles D. McGuffey, May 6, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Richard Twiss, May 19, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington [sender unclear], May 23, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to annual reception with unaddressed envelope, June 24, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Ward M. Leaw, July 12, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from George Putnam Smith, October 8, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from B. F. Burnham with typed poem pasted on reverse side, October 31, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington [sender unclear], December 3, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Brothers of the Xi from Allan P. Ball, June 15, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to annual reception to "Rev. and Mrs. W. North Rice," June 23, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Brothers of the Xi from Allan P. Ball, October 12, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Brothers of the Xi from H. P. Schaffer, December 8, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Brothers of the Xi from E...(?) W. Capen, March 18, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to annual reception, June 28, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Xi Chapter letter concerning the year's events, June 10, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notice of (unnamed) event put on by Xi Chapter, June 25, ? (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notice of (unnamed) event put on by Xi Chapter, June 21, ? (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Invitation to reception, June 17, ? (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Business card of Edward Witherspoon, organist and choirmaster of Church of the Redeemer, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Xi Chapter letter requesting alumni cooperation and participation, May 25, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to members announcing upcoming initiation ceremony, September 21, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising letter to members, April 12, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Xi Chapter letter to alumni, June 11, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to 77th annual initiation banquet, c. 1920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to 79th annual initiation banquet, November 3, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to 80th annual initiation banquet, about 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    First of two invitations to the "Eightieth Annual Initiation," but the two invitations refer to different dates and initiates.
  - Invitation to 80th annual initiation banquet, about 1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Second of two invitations to the "Eightieth Annual Initiation," but the two invitations refer to different dates and initiates.
  - Invitation to Musicale, October 26, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Invitation to memorial service for Herbert L. Bridgman, November 1924 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Invitation to 82nd annual initiation banquet, October 27, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to 85th annual initiation, November 1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to "special initiation," May 1928 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to "special Initiation and Banquet," about 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to initiation ceremony, about 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Announcement of new pledges from the classes of 1929 and 1931, about 1928 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to "Special Initiation," February 1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to a "Special initiation," April 1932 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Mack Goode from B. R. Buckingham, February 13, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to alumni seeking help with new rushing campaign, February 23, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Unsigned letter [presumably from Karl Harrington] seeking information from Xi alumni about their experiences in the fraternity for a new history book, June 21, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Frank B. Wade providing information for Harrington's new history Xi Chapter, June 25, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from F. E. Porter providing information for Harrington's new history of Xi Chapter, undated but presumably 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Fredric W. Frost providing information for Harrington's new history of Xi Chapter, July 11, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from F. E. Porter, July 16, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Robert W. Gillispie declining to contribute to Harrington's new history of Xi Chapter, July 30, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from Charles ? providing information for Harrington's new history of Xi Chapter, September 16, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter inviting alumni to initiation banquet from S. Roberts Rose, February 2, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Karl Harrington from M. Eugene Culver, February 13, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from John S. Barton seeking support for rushing campaign, February 22, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Order form for Karl Harrington's history of the Xi Chapter, April 29, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from John S. Barton inviting them to commencement weekend, May 24, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to secretary of Xi Chapter from Norman M. Brown (secretary of Epsilon Phi Chapter), October 2, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from James von Benschoten Dresser inviting them to initiation ceremony, January 21, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from H. G. Travis encouraging members to purchase Karl Harrington's history of Xi Chapter, February 5, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from M. H. Matthes requesting new photo of chapter house, March 12, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi brothers from Benjamin T. Burton of the Alumni Association, March 16, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from Murray Pomeroy George inviting them to commencement weekend, May 20, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi brothers from Benjamin T. Burton concerning the Alumni Association, November 6, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Charles Daniel Brodhead, December 12, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from James P. Parker inviting members to dinner dance, December 3, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Ben Badenoch inviting members to gathering, December 12, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Benjamin T. Burton inviting members to convention, March 8, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Benjamin T. Burton, March 18, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from Walt Bennett inviting them to commencement weekend, June 5, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to alumni from Jib Stacey inviting them to initiation ceremony, February 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Connecticut members from Ward P. Bates inviting them to dinner, February 10, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to John T. Hancock from Nancy Ford, November 1, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to alumni from John T. Hancock inviting them to initiation ceremony, February 9, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Benjamin T. Barton inviting members to convention, April 24, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Stephen G. Kent, May 18, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Congratulatory telegram to Xi freshmen from Mr. and Mrs. Black Don Smith, September 20, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Congratulatory telegram to Xi Chapter from Joe Zaro, September 21, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Mr. Benson from Anne ?, September 22, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from S. P. Cohen inviting members to Kappa Chapter house, October 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to members from John J. Chester inviting them to Gamma Chapter house, February 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Includes newspaper clipping about Gamma involvement in university athletics
  - Postcard to "'Lou,' 'Moe,' 'Pope' '42" from "Mothy," October 28, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Announcement of engagement of Charles Taber and Elinore Holland, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invitation to gathering at Theta Chapter house, November 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from John Gibson, November 9, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invitation to luncheon at Beta Beta Chapter, November 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Helen A. Mackeleau, November 25, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Initiation announcement from Rho Chapter, November 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Theta Review, December 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Pi Garnet, December 23, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invitation to initiation ceremony of Omicron Chapter, about 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invitation to initiation ceremony of Theta Chapter, about 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from James McConaughy, January 4, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Iota Owl, February 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Psi News, March 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Pi Garnet, April 1, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Postcard to Xi Chapter from Jim Langhurst, April 2, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Invitation to initiation ceremony of Iota Chapter, May 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Initiation announcement from Eta Chapter, about 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Initiation announcement from Omega Chapter, about 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Initiation announcement from Pi Chapter, about 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Pledging announcement from Upsilon Chapter, about 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Pledging announcement from Theta Theta Chapter, about 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Acknowledgement of expression of sympathy from Mrs. Harold Mine and Mr. and Mrs. Thomas M. Hine, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter seeking subscriptions to The Annals of Psi Upsilon, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter from Fremont Rider, librarian at Olin Library, thanking donor for gift of The Annals of Psi Upsilon, 1833-1941, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter from Fremont Rider, librarian at Olin Library, thanking donor for gift of The Annals of Psi Upsilon, 1833-1941, and Karl Harrington's history of Xi Chapter, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Xi Chapter from Elizabeth Stone Gregory, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to secretary of Xi Chapter from J. Lyman Hurlbut, January 18, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letter to President of Xi Chapter from Eleanor L. Welch, April 26, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letter to President of Xi Chapter from Eleanor L. Welch, April 30, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letter to Eleanor Welch from Kenneth D. Krier, May 2, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letter to Kenneth D. Krier from John E. Fricke, May 25, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Invitation to Karl Harrington from H. F. Robertson, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unopened envelope addressed to "Prof. C. S. Harrington, City," undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Invitation to Xi Chapter event, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified letter, later marked with name "W. H. Boughton," undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters to the Xi of Psi Upsilon, Beginning in Fall Term of 1882 (Box 12)
    Scrapbook collection of letters
  - Psi Upsilon Communications from Executive Council, April 10, 1920-February 16, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Letter boxes
    - Lettersundated
      - Unsorted, 1881-1903 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - A, 1893-1898 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - B, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - C, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - E, 1886-1904 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - F-G, 1886-1899 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - H, 1897-1901 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - I-K, 1876-1896 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - L-M, 1885-1895 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - N-O, 1881-1903 (Box 3, Folder 10-12)
      - P-Q, 1869-1903 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
      - R, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - S, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - T, 1891-1894 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - W, 1879-1901 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Chapter letters
      - A, 1886-1897 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - B, 1884-1895 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - C, 1886-1895 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - D, 1886-1897 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - E, 1886-1892 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - F, 1887-1891 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - G, 1886-1895 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - H, 1891-1892 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - I-J, 1887-1895 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - K, 1887-1897 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - L, 1886-1897 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - M, 1889-1892 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Mc, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - P-Q, 1881-1897 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - S, 1887-1895 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - T, 1886-1892 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - U-V, 1886-1891 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - W, 1885-1895 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - X-Z, 1887-1892 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Personal letters
      - A, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - B, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - C, 1896-1907 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - D, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - E, 1896-1900 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - F, 1894-1904 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - G, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - H, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - I-J, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - K, 1896-1901 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - L, 1896-1901 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - M, 1896-1902 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Mc, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - N, 1896-1903 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - O, 1898-1899 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - P-Q, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - R, 1898-1904 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - S, 1896-1902 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - T, 1896-1904 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - U-V, 1897-1904 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - W, 1897-1904 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Personal letters
      - Misc., 1888-1893 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Special, 1888-1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - A, 1886-1894 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - B, 1887-1895 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - C, 1886-1895 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - D, 1887-1895 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - E, 1888-1889 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - F, 1891-1895 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - G, 1884-1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - H, 1887-1895 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - I-J, 1888-1895 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - K, 1884-1896 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - L, 1886-1893 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - M, 1888-1895 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Mc, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - N, 1886-1895 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - P-Q, 1888-1895 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - R, 1886-1895 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - S, 1884-1896 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - T, 1882-1895 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - V, 1891-1892 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - W, 1873-1895 (Box 6, Folder 22)